Gus: Hey Eddy
Eddy: Yeah
Gus: We need to bring the c100 downtown 'cause we're shooting with Dom at 2 okay?
Eddy: Ok.
Gus: Oh hey, real quick. Do you want to grab the, uh, the little binder clips?
Eddy: Yeah sure
Gus: Okay. Sounds good.
Hey one more thing, I need you to--
Urgh!
Eddy: What?
*shakes cup*
*clinking of crayons hitting tabletop*
There's a bunch of crayons in here
Eddy: What?
Gus: Yeah, there's just...
Like I was just drinking water I thought and there's just a bunch of crayons.
Eddy: There's crayons in your cup?
Gus: That's weird. Well, let's grab another one.
Yeah, and we need to finish those scripts by next Tuesday too
otherwise Bill said he's not gonna help us with the lighting in-
Oh my God ??
Well, there's crans in this cup too!
Eddy: more crans???
Gus: Do you think there's crans in the other cups?
Eddy: Yeah, you've gotta check if we have crayons in our house
Gus: Yeah?!!
Eddy: what??
Gus: I don't know??
Oh my goodness they're in the bowls too!
Eddy: There's crans in the bowls??
Gus: There's crans in the bowls!!
Eddy: Why ??
Gus: I just don't know the source of all these crayons!
Eddy: Do you think there's crans in the cabinets or?
Gus: Well, frankly I'm almost afraid to check!
Eddy: Well, you have to
Gus: well here we go
OHHHHHHHHHHHHHH
There are crans in the cupboards too!
Eddy: Why are there crans in the cupboard dude???
Gus: there's more and more!!
Eddy: Check the other cupboard then!!
Gus: I'll do it, I'll do that
Should I check this cupboard too?
Eddy: Yeah!
Check that cupboard!!
Gus: I'll do it!
AHHHHHHHHHHH
LOOK AT ALL THE CRAYONS IN THE CUPBOAARRRDD
*screaming and yelling from both parties*
There's more and m o r e
I don't know if you saw but this goes WAY back
oh my god they're coming out
there's so many crans in here dude
Eddy: Why're there so many??
Gus: I don't know there's so many crayons, hundreds or thousands of them
There's just crayons everywhere!!
Eddy: wait, is it...
Is it crans or crayons?
Gus: Well I've been saying crans like c r a n s -- crans
Eddy: Yeah, we've been-- I was saying that, you just said crayons
Gus: Crayon?
Eddy: Crayon?
Gus: Crayon
Eddy: Crayan
Gus: Cran. I don't know, Google it?
Eddy: Ugh! Dude!
Google is crayons now!!
Gus: *exasperated scream* OH NOOOO
Eddy: What am I gonna look up stuff with now??
Gus: You can't, it's just crayyoonnss
Eddy: Do you think Bing is crayons??
Gus: Well I don't use it, but I hope not
Eddy: I still won't, obviously
Gus: I still wouldn't, even it was the only available search engine
I won't use it
Eddy: What else is crans??
Gus: I don't know
I don't know, this might be crans-- this might be
Eddy: *horrified screaming* oh it's crans
Gus: look it's so many crans
Eddy: check the drawers
*on verge of tears* check the drawers
Gus: look at the drawers over here
The oven!! [unintelligible screaming about crayons in oven]
*horrified gasp*
Eddy: it's c r a n s
Gus: *crying* I need a tissue
C L E A R L Y ITS CRANS
Eddy: *horrified scream*
I don't know what we were expecting at this point but it's s t i l l  c r a n s
Eddy: *crying* it's all crans
Dude I can't sweep fast enough, there's too many crans!!
Gus: I know, there's too many--
What--
oh my god
Eddy: it's in the faBRIC
Gus: I can't--
Eddy: It's in the FABRIC
Gus: tHiS iS POlYEstER
Eddy: ??????'?? ?????? ???????? ?????????????????
Gus: Well that was gross!
Eddy: Check your room, dude
Gus: I will check my room
Eddy: Check your room
Gus: I'm afraid to look, almost
Oh man--
*unintelligible screaming from crayon attack*
*rugged breathing and gasping*
Oh I don't know what I--
*crying* EDDY
*dramatic sound effect*
Wow
Guess Eddie's crayons now
Do I... still call him Eddie? Or does he...
Do I... does I... could I call him Crans now?
Who's gonna pay rent, too? I don't think it's fair if I have to foot the whole bill
But... I'll figure that out I suppose
Eddy: Hey dude
I'm not... the crayons, I was just...
standing off to the side a little bit
Gus: *clears throat* oh, it's...
Good
*sniff*
should probably-- should-- should probably clean up these crayons
Eddy: Yeah, I was gonna say we should...
...clean up these... these crayons